This is Adam,
and he's the owner of Adapt Jiu Jitsu.
So you've been making good rash guards
since 2018?
Yep.
Sending them to Darren and I.
We're going to overlay pictures right now.
Yep.
You didn't ask for anything,
just sent us jujitsu rash guards.
Yeah.
Then you signed your death warrant
when you made the first
customized ones with New Tonic on.
And how many have I bought off you since?
Thousands.
And today I announce I am now an investor
in Adapt, so I am now your boss.
Shit.
Not quite. Still majority shareholder.
[laughs]
But it's not just us that have invested.
Who else has invested?
Darren-
The Turk-
And Paulo Lima.
The Turkish one, Darren Cartel,
Paulo Lima.
So some of you may have noticed
that Adapt, for a start,
if they didn't do the best
rash guards, I just wouldn't wear them,
for a start.
Colors, the pastel ones you've done,
amazing.
One thing I like is the elastic on this.
Stops your belly from coming out in a
roll. Go on, Declan, have a feel of that.
Oh, God, do you know what that feels like?
Money, future, investment.
We've also got these underarm vents.
Look at that.
That stops the rash guard from smelling as
quickly and keeps you a little bit
cooler as well while you're training.
So one of the first reasons
that I started buying so many was
that I thought this
was just really good real estate.
So the same way that when I was competing,
every
time I put someone in a guilty
and I tapped, so my brand on the back
was amazing.
As you can tell,
I like putting brands on stuff,
including the car.
So I was wearing your rash guards, I
was a massive fan of your rash guards,
and I
thought it just made sense.
You're a black belt in jujitsu.
I'm soon to be a black belt in jujitsu.
Let's take my marketing, your brand,
and let's show people the
synergy that can be there.
So let's have a look at the ecosystem.
So we've got Adapt Jiu Jitsu.
We won't have to talk numbers, numbers,
but we were
talking about some of the eCom statistics
the other day.
Roughly out of 100 visits to the website,
you get?
We've got a 2% conversion rate on average.
Obviously,
that depends on the month of the year.
But,
yeah, 2%.
So that means every 50 visits to the
website will work out to
be a sale.
And you know we were talking about this on
the beach yesterday.
I was actually keen to show you this
and visualize it.
So you obviously got your way of running a
business.
I've got my way of how I would run it.
I would say we have a funnel here,
and the bottom part to have this statistic
is
great. Now,
from an optimization standpoint,
we could look
into if we change the website a little
bit, if we A/B split some thumbnails, we
could take that to 40 visits, 30 visits,
20 visits.
Exactly, yeah.
Also,
I believe that as the brand just begets
more exposure in front of people,
people will see it. That will improve.
But for me,
I think the easiest thing would be to just
leave that as is and then
move up one stage.
So the next thing we need to look at
is traffic.
And I know traffic can seem like such a
weird and odd topic to talk about,
but this is where we're going to use the
leverage of Paulo Lima, Darren Cartel, and
myself. Because ultimately,
as social media creators, our only
job is to send traffic to websites.
That's all we do.
And in a perfect world,
we have a business where people go,
once they land, certain
amount of visits, certain amount of sales.
So some of the creatives
that we could use from this,
I think even just putting
it out there for other businesses to
listen, they're going to go,
"That's a good
idea. I can apply
that to mine." So first of all,
wearing it is going to be
one of the main ways
that you're going to market it.
We've spoken about creatives.
Yep.
What was the one
that I told you about
that I want you to do in Clapham Park?
Well, exactly. It was a bit gutting.
Do a deal with him,
and then the first thing he wants me to do
is go to Clapham
Common and fight a load of people to see
if they can tap me out.
But the thing is, if he does a video-
[laughs]
... and it is, "Tap me out,
win 100 pounds.
Tap me out, win 500 pounds. Tap me out,
win a free rash guard," whatever, we can
get attention and traffic and eyeballs.
Because if you do a video about a rash
guard, it's going to be quite difficult to
get views.
That video will get more views than this
one.
So we have wearing it, content. Also,
another
area that I quite like-
What have I got myself into, Declan?
What have I got myself into?
So you've got athletes,
but the athletes you have within the brand
are actually
sound. Like Conor's BJJ.
Got Suzy.
Suzy, who, your weapon. She
was the first one to win a comp in the
gloves-
Yes, she was
... with the eyes on.
So you've got this cool band of athletes.
Then the lady who just won trials?
Injana.
Injana Goodman.
Well done.
She had some killers in her division.
Absolute beast, yeah.
So you've got your athletes out there as
well, but I've also said there's a way
that in my world we could mix content with
the athletes.
So I've said that maybe we take Conor,
who I was training with only a few weeks
ago. We send him to a competition,
and just before he steps on the mat, you
say, "Here's 500 pounds.
If you win the division,
you get to keep it.
But if you lose,
we're going to give this to whoever beats
you." And that to me is
just raising the stakes so
that you could have a reel,
but rather it's being like,
"Hey, my name's Adam.
I'm the owner of Adapt Jiu Jitsu." It's,
"Hi, my name's Adam.
We're at a competition.
Conor's one of our athletes, and
if he wins this
competition,
we're going to give him a bonus of 500
pounds.
But if he loses,
he's got to give it to the person
that beats him." Straight away,
we've created a scenario,
we've created a story.
So there is a mixture of that.
And yesterday we were
talking about a few things,
and we can talk about this here.
I'm interested to get Declan's opinion.
You've got a nice aesthetic on your page
at the moment-
Yep
... for Adapt Jiu Jitsu.
So I would say that's your social media
here.
How many followers you got? Nearly 10K,
right?
Yeah, 10K.
Cool.
There is a hesitation held by the group of
investors that you want
to keep that aesthetic.
Yes.
But my argument is surely traffic
is the most important
thing. And how many posts have you done?
650, something like that.
For me, for a business that
was founded in 2018, when did you
start the Instagram?
It would've been shortly after that.
We call it since 2021
that we actually started taking the
business seriously
after COVID,
and I've been working full-time on it now
since 2022.
Doesn't look like full-time, mate.
That looks like a post a day for two
years.
What do you reckon, Declan? 650 posts.
Could be a bit more, couldn't it?
Could be a bit more, mate.
Considering we know
that every 50 visits you get one
sale, there's a part of me that thinks,
"Oh,
do you not want more sales?" That's me
as an investor.
Now I come along to your business and
when I'm auditing it, I'm
like, "Oh, that aesthetic or
that certain look you're trying to have
could
potentially be hindering the very next
steps we need." I'm not saying like ruin
it
or whatever, but yes, we've got that.
So,
ads, running much?
Yeah. Not spending a lot, but yeah,
we haven't got anyone doing the ads.
I do them all myself.
I taught myself how to do Facebook ads,
Google ads.
I edit the videos myself, so yeah,
we do it.
We-
Would you say it works?
We consistently get- Between a two
and a half and a
3X ROAS. So yes, it works. The problem
is scaling.
We've never really tried to scale,
and obviously it's very hard to keep that
ROAS when you start to really put some
money behind the budget, which is when we
need to get some professionals in to do
that.
Return on ad spend.
And also everyone thinks, oh,
you're just tripling your money.
It's not that simple.
It's not that.
Because even with the mentorship,
when you get to a point,
you get exhaustion,
fatigue,
you have to stay on top of the ads.
Also,
I think that should we want to nail ads
or just increase traffic,
I think traffic's so much easier.
That's basically break-even point.
A three ROAS will break even for us.
When you're talking about your admin fees,
your website, your tax, your
photo shoots, and everything like that,
you need that three ROAS just to break
even.
Because UK is pretty savage.
We don't have to go into the full
economics
of it, but say you sell a rash guard.
What's the RRP on a rash guard?
Between £50 and £60.
Cool. Now, if anyone
was watching this video
and wanted to buy one to try one out
because they do jujitsu,
would you offer a money-back guarantee?
Absolutely.
What's your email address?
Adam@adaptjj.com. If it's a really nasty
bit of feedback,
make sure you contact James for now.
That's what we're paying him for.
So there you go. Just zoom in on
that for a sec, Dec,
if anyone does want to get a
refund. But the good thing here
is we can start from the top.
You buying that means you get a good rash
guard. I wear an XL, for the record.
You wear a large, Declan.
You're an XL as well.
Straight away, all the people
that buy those, my shareholding
is going up.
Welcome to the layer cake, kids. Okay,
so you sell that. First thing, VAT.
Yeah.
So let's-
20% comes off the top straight away.
So let's look at £60, for instance.
So 12 pound.
Wow. I hate VAT.
It's the worst.
I don't understand it.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's 10% here for our GST and that side.
20% just gone.
Yeah.
If they tried to impose
that in any other world that didn't exist,
there'd
be riots in the street. Okay.
We don't have to talk about cost of rash
guard.
Yep.
We don't have to talk about anything like
that. Staffing, facilities.
Where I would sell digital products,
when someone joins,
we just give them digital access.
But shipping on average?
Shipping, it costs us,
it's about 4.95 for the customer to ship.
Yeah. And-
And that basically just covers our cost
because we've got a fulfillment center.
We use a 3PL, which
is a small business locally to where we
are.
They obviously collect all our stock
when it's delivered from our suppliers.
They put it on shelf,
they do stock counts,
and then they'll pack that up and ship
it to the customer.
So we don't make any money on the
shipping.
What the customer pays for shipping goes
towards obviously the postage
label from Royal Mail or DHL,
whoever we use, and then the cost of the
warehouse as well.
Is the gray one going to be on sale soon?
Yeah, these two are new. These
are going to be coming out within the next
couple of
months.
The gray one with the eye?
Yeah. Oh, with the eye? Yeah, no,
that's going to be here within the next
two
weeks.
So they'll be on sale within the next two
If someone heads to your website now-
Yeah
... or have you got a newsletter
or somewhere?
So say someone's watching this video-
Yeah
... they want the one with the eye,
it's coming out in two weeks.
Yeah.
Have you got a pre-sale option?
We could set that up for sure. But
if you go on the website,
you'll get hit with
the pop-up,
which is to sign up to the newsletter.
That's where I write all the emails
myself,
so you'll get notified as soon as they
come on sale.
All of the people on the newsletter will
get notified before anyone
else, before it goes on Instagram
or anything like that.
Reason being,
we haven't got a lot of them,
so we're going to do a certain amount
undecided, and then that's going to be it.
So you need to make-
So here's something for you to do.
If you give me the link for that,
we'll put it
in the description to this video,
then people should sign up to it.
Not just so they can get a rash guard,
but they can watch some of the marketing
stuff we're going to do-
Yep
...
over the next few months to grow this
business.
Yep.
Okay. So already nearly £20 of that
is gone just in VAT and shipping.
Any other costs? I suppose your staff.
Yeah. So you've got me.
We pay our athletes.
You've got to pay for the marketing,
so the
photo shoots.
To actually get the products on the
website, what other costs have we
got? We've got the-
The actual rash guard
... the actual rash guard itself.
Then you've got your subscriptions as
well.
So whether that be the website cost,
all of the apps involved in the website to
be
able to give people a good experience,
it adds up.
So that's more so just the point.
When people see £60 for a rash guard,
they're not
just paying for that-
No
...
they're paying for a lot of other things
that are in there. Okay.
There's also the tough thing for you guys
is when you produce a rash guard,
how many different sizes have you got to
make it in?
Yeah, so this is the problem, and this
is actually what we do different to
everyone
else.
So you've got five main men's sizes
or unisex sizes.
We also do every single one of our
designs, we're the only company
that I know of
in the whole world
that does every single design in five
women's sizes as well.
So they're shaped differently,
and they range from extra extra small
women's to
large women's, as well as the men's sizes.
So that's 10 sizes of each design.
Let's just do this quickly.
Extra extra small.
Extra small.
Extra small. This is just for women,
right?
Yep. Small.
Small.
Medium, large.
Then you have the-
Then for men?
Then you have small, medium, large,
extra large, and then XXL.
So already,
for you to create a rash guard,
it's not like, "Oh, sweet,
we're going to be making 20,
30 pound profit." Straight away,
you're going to have
to have coverage in all those areas.
Yeah.
Because what you don't want
is to do all this marketing
and get all these athletes,
all this content, people wearing it,
and run paid ads, for you to then get to a
point where someone goes to the website
and you don't have the stock fulfilled.
Yeah.
So if you've got 10 SKUs of each rash
guard, we've got between 20 and 30
designs live on our website at any one
time.
So managing that is one of the biggest
jobs that I do.
Trying to figure out,
because you don't want stock just sitting
there for months at
a time not selling,
because that's just money on the shelf
that you could be using
for other stuff. Obviously,
all resources are limited.
You don't just have unlimited funds to
just order everything.
So it's very,
very difficult to manage that.
And obviously that
is extra difficult because we have an
extra five sizes for the
women, but it's something that just
was obvious for us to do.
I don't know why other brands don't do it.
The biggest brands in the world,
not going to call them out,
but they'll just do
extra small men's as their women's design,
or some of the other biggest brands,
they'll just have two
or three women's designs.
So that's not good enough for us.
We like to just do it the same for every
design, five women's, five men's, and
causes a few headaches,
but it's got to be done.
So Darren and Lima like to wear the gi a
lot.
What do you do different about the gis?
Last few years,
we haven't focused a lot on the gis.
We've got our signature white gi,
our signature black gi,
and we've just focused on
just those two for now.
With the gis comes a whole different array
of
problems. The size of them to start,
so they're harder to store
and they're harder
to ship.
So you can add $10 to $15 sometimes Just
shipping from our supplier per unit to get
here, and then obviously storage is a
bit more expensive.
Shipping them to customers
is more expensive.
If you're getting an international order,
postage goes way up.
So the margin's a lot lower.
They're harder to store, harder to ship.
So we focused all our resources,
most of our resources, on rash guards
and shorts.
That's going to change with you guys.
We're going to have a few more resources
to hand, so we can start doing a few more
gis.
And the thing that comes from my
investment is we can give you a lump of
cash too.
So if we have an inclination we think this
rash guard's going to do well-
Yeah
... we can go, "Here's cash. Go buy it."
Yeah.
Don't dip into our in stores.
Let's run discounts.
Let's run promotions or whatever.
And what that allows us to do as well
is buy in volume.
So once you get into the ordering hundreds
and thousands of gis,
you can start paying for shipping
containers.
So things come here by ship, by sea,
rather than getting flown in, which
is obviously a lot more expensive to fly
things in.
When you're ordering smaller quantities
like we have been doing, it's a lot more
expensive. So when we place bigger orders,
and now we can place bigger orders,
those costs are going to come down,
because we're able to ship things as well.
So here's a
question for you. Now,
there's all well and good making great
quality
products,
but the one thing I want to get into
is why people should wear Adapt.
Now, one thing that I think we can do,
let's say for the next three months,
off the
back of this video,
if someone buys an Adapt rash guard,
wears its competition,
and you win,
I'll send you some Nutonix myself.
And what I'm doing now
is I'm cross-leveraging my ecosystems.
So I'm using my Nutonic brand to help
Adapt, because Adapt has been helping
Nutonic.
So this is where there's kind of synergy
between it, because if you like
Nutonic enough,
we've got a rash guard where you can have
that synergy
between it. Whereas if you like Adapt
and you like Nutonic or whatever, that
synergy I think is quite cool.
So as a reason,
I don't think any of the other
companies, if you
were to wear their thing to a tournament
and win, the company's
not going to be like, "Oh,
nice rash guard," unless you're a
sponsored athlete.
Where I want to do something that's more
centric to everyday people wearing the
rash guard, not the-
Yeah
... not the athletes.
Yeah.
If you're one of the best jujitsu guys in
the world and you win, cool.
But like with Suzy and other people,
any of you guys that wear Adapt from this
point on in this video,
if you go win a tournament,
and I'll check the bracket on
the smooth comp.
If you're there because there
was only one person at the
tournament-
[laughs]
... and everyone doesn't turn up,
I'll check that,
and I'll see you had walkovers.
But if you win with a meaningful amount,
tag Adapt, tag me.
If I miss it, he'll see it, and we'll go,
"Well done.
As an Adapt competitor,
we'll send you some stock."
And that's where the comp team rash guard
comes in, so that new one that we're
launching. Let me get it. Hang on.
So yeah,
we've come up with this idea of having a
competition team.
So yeah, the back of that,
the whole idea of the comp team is
that you have a
little bunch of people that wear Adapt
and go compete on behalf.
We're going to run maybe a little
membership.
Yeah.
Some exclusive perks.
We could do seminars.
Yeah.
Instructionals.
I'm actually going to do an instructional
soon.
Would you just send it to everyone on the
database? Might as well.
Yeah, can do.
So-
Anyone on our mailing list,
anyone wants to sign up to the mailing
list, for sure.
I tell you what,
for those of you watching this,
I've got a guillotine variation
that no one's using.
Everyone's sleeping on it.
I'm going to film an instructional soon,
and we'll send it to everyone on the Adapt
email list.
So make sure you sign up below. Oh,
where was I?
Okay, so 50 visits, traffic, socials.
For me, the lowest hanging fruit
is going to be post more, and
I want creatives. I want techniques,
because I don't think there's ever a
shortfall of those.
But I want those techniques to have some
really good hooks.
If you want to tap high belts,
consider doing this.
If you want to take a black belt's back,
you'll need to consider this.
If you want to win at competition,
do this.
If you can't finish your guillotines,
try this technique.
Most people are leg locking wrong because
they do this.
We need to have a statement in the
beginning that gets people to want to
watch.
So you've got some really good high-level
athletes, but they're like, "Right, guys,
today we're going to look at a technique
of using the wizzer for a takedown." And
you're like, "That's boring.
They've gone." Instead, some people
are trained you
just can't take down, but
if you use this technique,
you'll get them down all the
time,
to the point they're probably going to
pull guard. Let me show you.
So we need to be sexy with the first five
seconds.
First five seconds sexy.
Another thing would be
variety. I said to you
that I want to see some...
So imagine you've got a famous person,
Declan.
Maybe
not the person I was going to say.
Famous people from history, and there's
iconic photos of them,
and you just AI put them in an Adapt rash
guard, and be
like, "Yeah, do you know what?
Steve Irwin, what a guy. Great guy.
Highlight was when I met him
and he wore an Adapt rash guard."
And everyone would
go, "Hold on,
he died before the business was formed.
Shut your fucking mouth." So have some fun
with that.
Who's a really famous person you look up
to?
Anthony Joshua wearing our new Adapt rash
guard.
He's got a little suit printed all over
it.
[laughs]
Oh,
I had the pleasure of meeting Paul Walker
before he died.
Yeah.
He's so good to you and that stuff.
And I think you can have some fun with
that,
people commenting on it, being like,
"LOL," laughing faces, whatever.
But the thing that I
was saying to you before is,
because he was a bit unsure on
this stuff, he's not sure
if he wants to see Paul Walker in an Adapt
rash guard.
But with every single thing
that you try from a social standpoint,
you're probably going to build to traffic,
and then that traffic's going to build
to visits.
So we get to determine campaign A, let's
say, is funny.
You might double the traffic.
Sales might remain the same.
You might go techniques.
Traffic might half,
but the conversions might go up.
So every single thing here, in my eyes,
needs to be tested.
Then the traffic on the website needs to
be monitored, because it will come in
peaks and troughs.
And then you just need to look at your
conversions.
Because ultimately, if visits go up-
But the conversion percentage
goes down.
It depends how many sales you get per
marketing effort.
So, what I'm trying to say is,
it might be 10 times easier to get views
with
funny stuff.
It might half your conversion, but
that would still net to more sales.
Alternatively, the techniques that
were too long or too boring,
they might only
send 20 visits,
but you might get one sale from it.
But if you tried this before,
I would say keep doing what you're doing,
because
seeing as you just haven't even tried
this.
Yeah. So then, next thing above here would
be paid.
So let's think about ways we could do
paid.
Again, I don't really like the idea of
paying athletes like super world champions
or whatever, because that £5,000 a
month you give them,
I think could be better gifting stock-
I agree
...
and Nutonic to the actual everyday
athletes-
Yeah
... which we're reliant on.
So I don't really like the idea of paid
athletes.
Ads, I like the idea of ads,
but it's not the main thing
that I want to do,
because again,
that money you spent on ads,
I think you could end up just gifting.
When it comes to paid stuff,
I think videographer.
If you're young and hungry,
and want to work for Adam,
there's his email address
again. I might even fucking hire
that cunt for you,
because I want five reels a
day, Adam. I want more than that.
I want trial reels, 10 reels a day.
Traffic, traffic, traffic, money, money,
money. Trying to get my ROI myself.
So, videographer would be a pro for paid.
So rather than paying an athlete £5,000 a
month to wear your shirt, you could give
a videographer £2,500 a month
and go full time.
Contracts and negotiations open to
negotiations.
Because I think you get such a better
return on investment from that.
I know I've said this before,
I feel like you need a HQ.
Yeah.
I feel that you need a space like this,
but in the
UK.
And I've already mapped out where you
live, where Darren lives, where Alima
lives, and where my mom and dad live,
and we've already got an area there.
We need a matted out gym.
The gym runs at break even, so the
members contribute to whatever they pay,
pretty much cancels out
your rent. We have a shop on site, so
when people come in to train for seminars,
you say, "Hey guys,
grab yourself a rash guard from there."
Also means people can
size up stuff. You
could even have trial rash guards
and stuff.
So if someone comes in wearing one of your
competitors, you'd be like, "Oh, you
can't wear that for this session.
But you can wear any of these here on
this."
[laughs]
Then you can go like sauna, ice showers,
whatever.
And yeah,
I think you can do so much with that.
I think your headquarters,
you could even keep stock on site
if you wanted to.
And that would work well for the content
as well, right?
Yeah.
If you've got a place to film it,
you've got a cool space,
there's so much you
could do with that.
Yeah.
You pretty much need exactly one of these.
If I wasn't so selfish using this as a
gym, I'd just turn this into a jiu-jitsu
gym. We can mat out downstairs.
This would actually be a pretty sick
jiu-jitsu gym,
wouldn't it?
Yeah.
James gave me the fob for this place as
well.
So I now just come here
and sleep here in the evenings
when he's not looking.
Yeah, fine.
Save a bit of money on hotels
when I'm here.
That's it. So we've got a videographer.
What do you reckon as well, Declan?
As far as paid things
that could benefit this part of the
ecosystem.
And I think obviously,
we haven't even really mentioned it,
but you guys as well,
like you, Paul, and Darren-
Yeah, to be fair-
Plugging into your networks as well with
the right sort of content, making it
relevant.
Obviously not all of the followers
are going to be relevant for jujitsu,
but there's still a big base there.
So let's say
this is where I think us three come into
it.
Argo, James, Paul, Darren. The JPD.
I think our objective
is to just fuel these two things.
So we can create content for you guys,
which we're going to do.
Whether it be skits, instructionals,
competing.
You see how much attention Alima's getting
competing at IFGBB Worlds,
whatever.
[laughs]
So then also, it's in our interest
that we start adding Adapt to our
newsletters,
start doing promotions every once in a
while.
So this is the part where we can do the
most.
Then actually, either end of this, this
is going to be your domain here, where I
do think you just try
and monitor those conversions.
But the conversion of 2% I actually think
is fine.
So many people out there are like, "Eh,
2%."
No, it's fine.
If you got to 3%,
it would be 33% more sales.
I'm like, instead of focusing on that,
this part here is the part.
I actually think this part's the easy
part.
Yeah.
Headquarters might run at a slight loss,
but the beautiful thing here is
where most jujitsu gyms
are running to try and make money, and be
profitable, and be super wealthy,
that just becomes a full-time
advertising hub for the brand.
Yeah.
"Where'd you train?" "I train at Adapt."
"Oh, don't they do rash guards?" "Oh yeah,
they're a gym, too."
That could even run at a loss.
Let's say that runs at a loss of £2,000 a
month. Fine, send me the bill.
I'm coming to train.
Declan's really excited.
Make sure you record that bit, mate.
Make sure you record that bit.
Declan's really excited. But yeah, so
for me, as far as a business,
this bit's already done.
This bit needs to be done.
This bit just needs to be dialed up.
Because you have a successful jujitsu
business posting once every four days on
average.
What would you say to people out there
that are thinking, "I've already
got a rash guard?"
Unless it's an Adapt one,
you've got the wrong rash guard.
Look at that. You see that confidence?
I like it. What color should they go for?
You get the classic black rash guards
are great.
Original khaki rash guard's great.
And we've got all these new colors coming
out.
You've got 25 to choose from on there.
What happened to my fucking-
Take your pick
Where's that lid? My day is ruined.
Can't believe it.
What else haven't we covered?
We've just set up all our bundles.
So yeah, another lever you can pull
when you're talking about any sort of
e-commerce thing, and I know you guys
are dealing with this with Nutonic as
well.
Average order value
is one of the biggest levers you can
pull to increase your revenue
and obviously your profitability.
So, combining things, doing a deal,
buy two items, get a
discount.
We've just introduced our essential
bundle.
So you can now go on the website,
get a white or a black gi.
You can get the black rash guard
and black shorts.
I think you save something like 50
or 60 quid.
So you get a really good deal,
and we ship out three items at once,
which ups our average order value.
So it's just a win-win for everyone.
So some quick jargon here. AOV,
average order value, and
CPA, which is cost per acquisition.
Yeah.
So even if we were to use paid, or we
were to use a videographer, or you
were to use headquarters, this
is still a cost per acquisition.
Yeah.
Then the socials, there's a cost.
Your wages, your time, whatever.
The traffic, there is a cost.
Also,
even if that traffic comes from Alima,
or Darren, or myself, that has come at
a cost-
Yeah
... shareholder dilution.
So there's always a cost per acquisition.
So once someone gets to
that point of sale, the lowest hanging
fruit is to increase the amount they buy.
Yes.
Because you've already spent so much to
get to this
point, that you do... And even if it
was only £10 more per
purchase-
Yeah
... if that takes them from 100 to 110,
that seems like only a
10% increase, but after costs
are deducted, that could be 20, 30, 40%
more money.
Yeah.
Which is massive to the profitability of
the business.
Especially when it comes to the shipping
as well.
You've got to remember,
it costs us the shipping label
and the fee from my
fulfillment center to pack it up.
That cost stays the same,
whether they're packing
one rash guard, which we make £50 from,
or that the value is £50,
or whether they put like six,
seven items in a thing and we sell like
£300 worth of stuff. The fixed cost
is the same.
So increasing the amount people buy
and that average order value
is one of the most
important things.
Fair amount of spotted a discrepancy.
How big is your email list?
6 to 7,000.
Wow!
Yeah. And we've got-
That's massive.
It's good.
So most of our sales come from emails
and actively-
Adam, say that again.
Most of our sales come from emails.
I feel validated right here. Sorry,
carry on.
So we've
got 6 to 7,000 people.
About 3,500 people open
my email every time I send one.
50% open rate.
Yeah.
Very good.
How often are you hitting the list?
So in terms of campaigns, try
and do one or two a week, not many.
As I say, I write all them myself.
We also have the flows as well.
So when you join the mailing list,
we have the sequences set up so you have a
five or six email flow.
Depending on whether people buy or not,
they'll drop out of
that flow at different points.
We then have other automations as well.
So abandoned cart automations. You've got
customer win-back,
people who haven't bought in a long time,
they'll kick into a
flow and get sent certain emails. So yeah,
there's a whole sort of web of emails.
If someone had a gym
and they wanted to do custom kit for the
entire gym-
Yep
... they just get in touch with you?
Yep.
And they could do designs?
Yeah.
So we'll help you out with all the
designs. You don't need to be a designer.
All we need is your logos
that you want on the kit in vector
format, which is something
that a lot of people don't have.
So if you're a gym owner
and you're getting a designer to design
your logos and
stuff,
make sure you get them to send it to you
in vector.
Yeah,
and then we can help you out with
everything. We'll deal with all of it.
It's a minimum of 30 units at the moment,
so you can mix and match between 15
shorts, 15 rash guards. All the prices
are on the website.
We've got a landing page on the website.
And we'll give you all the different
sizes,
because you said get this amount large,
this amount extra large, this much more.
Exactly, yeah.
We've got all the sales data from five
years of selling product now,
so we know how many of what size to order.
Adam, you need to shoot to open mat.
I can't join you because I pulled my lower
back because I'm 36 and a half.
Good being in business with you. Oh,
we should do the thing from...
What is it? It's not "Predator"
when Arnie and-
It is "Predator."
Is it?
Yeah.
[hands slap]
Right. Click the link in the description.
Join the email list, not just for Adam,
but for me.
Not just for his business,
but now for mine.
Not just so he can make money,
so I can make money.
And if you don't want to do
that because you don't train jujitsu,
that's fine.
But you should train jujitsu.
You should train jujitsu.
Click this video here because YouTube
recommends that
you'll like it.